Guide to the U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
- Dockstader, Steven L., Delbert M. Nebeker, Ewing David W.., Publication (Box 8)
  - Employee Participation Groups: Are They for You?, 1983; Publication (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Item 1: Employe Participation Groups: Are They For You?, 1983; Publication (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - "The Judiciary, the Law and Industrial Relations: An American Perspective"., 1983; Publication (Box 8, Folder 86)
    August 3 - 17 1983
    - Item 1: The Judiciary, the Law and Industrial Relations: An American Perspective, 1983; Publication (Box 8, Folder 86)
      Author: Harry T. Edwards
  - Talk with Us, Work with Us., 1986; Publication (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Item 1: Talk With Us, Work With Us, 1986; Publication (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - "The Political Economy of Industrial Conflict: Britain and the United States"., 1983; Publication (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Item 1: The Political Economy of Industrial Conflict: Britain and the United States, 1983; Publication (Box 8, Folder 88)
      Author: Paul K. Edwards
  - "Quality Circles Are Safety Circles"., 1983; Publication (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Item 1: Quality Circles are Safety Circles, 1983; Publication (Box 8, Folder 89)
      Author: Stephen Edwards
  - "The Humanist Philosophy in Perspective"., 1984; Publication (Box 8, Folder 90)
    January 0 February 1984
    - Item 1: The Humanist Philosophy in Perspective, 1984; Publication (Box 8, Folder 90)
      Author: Frederick Edwards
  - "Evidence on Attitudes Toward Alternative Sharing Arrangements"., 1989; Publication (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Item 1: Evidence on Attitudes Toward Alternative Sharing Arrangements, 1989; Publication (Box 8, Folder 91)
      Author: Daniel Egan, Douglas J. Herrmann and Derek C. Jones
  - "Workers Take Over the Store"., 1983; Publication (Box 8, Folder 92)
    September 11 1983
    - Item 1: Workers Take Over the Store, 1983; Publication (Box 8, Folder 92)
      Author: John Egerton
  - "Scandinavian Design: On Participation and Skills"., Publication (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Item 1: Scandinavian Design: On Participation and Skill, Publication (Box 8, Folder 93)
      Author: Pelle Ehn
  - "GM's Quality Network"., 1989; Publication (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Item 1: GM's Quality Network, 1989; Publication (Box 8, Folder 94)
      Author: Robert C. Stempel and Donald F. Ephlin
      Notes: dialogue between Stempel (GM) and Ephlin (UAW)
  - "Negotiating Over Technological Change in Banking and Insurance"., 1984; Publication (Box 8, Folder 95)
    July - August 1984
    - Item 1: Negotiating over technological change in banking and insurance, 1984; Publication (Box 8, Folder 95)
      Author: Edythe Epstein
  - People and Productivity: A Challenge to Corporate America., 1982; Publication (Box 8, Folder 96)
    November 1982
    - Item 1: People and Productivity: A Challenge to Corporate America, 1982; Publication (Box 8, Folder 96)
      Author: Eugene Epstein
  - EEOC's Approach to Quality Assurance., 1985; Publication (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Item 1: EEOC's Approach to Quality Assurance, 1985; Publication (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Quality Assurance Pilot Program in the Baltimore District Office: A Case Study., 1985; Publication (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Item 1: Quality Assurance Pilot Project in the Baltimore District Office: A Case Study, 1985; Publication (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - 1985, Publication (Box 8, Folder 99)
- Examining Health Care Cost - Gardner, Margaret, Craig Littler., Publication (Box 9)
  - The Food Marketing Industry Speaks: 1989., Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: The Food Marketing Industry Speaks, 1989; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - "For More and More Workers, An End to the 9-to-5 Day"., 1977; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    April 4 1977
    - Item 1: For More and More Workers, An End to the 9-to-5 Day, 1977; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - "Think Tank on Jobs that Works"., 1987; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Think Tank on Jobs That Works: The Work in America Institute finds practical answers to tough employment questions, 1987; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Author: Daniel Forbes
  - Innovations in Post-School Skill Formation Markets., 1989; Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
    June 14 - 15 1989
    - Item 1: Innovations in Post-School Skill Formation Markets, 1989; Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Author: G.W. Ford
  - Center Report 6 -- Avenues for Growth., 1987; Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Center Report 6--Avenues for Growth, Life Education Planning Program: A Status Report on the UAW-Ford Program, 1987; Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Employee Involvement: A Handbook in the UAW-Ford Process for Local Unions and Management., 1980; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Employe Involvement: A Handbook on the UAW-Ford process for local unions and management, 1980; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - From Vision to Reality: The UAW and Ford Create New Directions in Employee Development and Training., 1986; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: From Vision to Reality: The UAW and Ford create new directions in employee development and training, 1986; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - The UAW-Ford Employee development and Training Program., 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Presentation to the President's Commission on Industrial Competitiveness Regarding the UAW-Ford Employe Development and Training Program and its Joint National Center, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Author: Thomas J. Pasco and Richard J. Collins
    - Item 2: General Information Summary, Through Second Quarter, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - UAW-Ford Joint Programs., 1988; Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: UAW-Ford Joint Programs, 1988; Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - "Job Enrichment Lessons from AT&T"., 1982; Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Job Enrichment Lessons from AT&T, 1982; Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Author: Robert N. Ford
      Notes: printed in Organizational Behavior and the Practice of Management by Hampton, Summer and Webber
  - "The 'Norumbega' Syndrome: Data Collection and Productivity in an HMO"., 1987; Publication (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: The 'Norumbega' Syndrome: Data Collection and Productivity in an HMO, 1987; Publication (Box 9, Folder 11)
      Author: Maury Forman, Marjorie Hillson and Philip Kropatkin
  - "Labor and Community Influentials: A Comparative Study of Participation and Imagery"., 1963; Publication (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Labor and Community Influentials: A Comparative Study of Participation and Imagery, 1963; Publication (Box 9, Folder 12)
      Author: William H. Form and Warren L. Sauer
  - "Foster Higgins Health Care Benefits Survey 1990"., 1991; Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Health Care Benefits Survey 1990, Preliminary Report, 1991; Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Item 2: Runaway Health Care Costs Spark Renewed Demand for Flexible Benefit Programs: More than One-Fourth of Employers Now Offer Flex Plans, Survey Finds, 1991; Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - "Semi-Autonomous Work Groups: An Alternative in Organizing Production Work?"., 1981; Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Semi-autonomous work groups: An alternative in organizing production work?, 1981; Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
      Author: Panagiotis N. Fotilas
  - "People Make Robots Work"., 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: People make robots work, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 15)
      Author: Fred K. Foulkes and Jeffrey L. Hirsch
  - "Full Employment, Product-Marketing Strategies and Other Considerations"., 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Full Employment, Product-Marketing Strategies, and Other Considerations, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 16)
      Author: Fred K. Foulkes and Anne Whitman
  - The 1992 Development Report Card for the States: Executive Summary., Publication (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: The 1992 Development Report Card for the States: Economic Benchmarks for State and Corporate Decision-Makers, Executive Summary, Publication (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - "Apprenticeships: From High School to High Skills"., 1992; Publication (Box 9, Folder 18)
    April 1992
    - Item 1: Apprenticeships: From High School to High Skills, 1992; Publication (Box 9, Folder 18)
      Author: Bob Filipczack
  - "Management"., 1977; Publication (Box 9, Folder 19)
    September 16 1977
    - Item 1: Management: The Team Approved at the Top, 1977; Publication (Box 9, Folder 19)
      Author: Elizabeth M. Fowler
  - "The Strategic Business Approach to Training"., 1987; Publication (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: The Strategic Business Approach to Training, 1987; Publication (Box 9, Folder 20)
      Author: Derwin A. Fox and Alfred M. Tarquinio
  - Conference on Employee Participation in Ownership and Management., 1987; Publication (Box 9, Folder 21)
    October 6 1987
    - Item 1: Conference on Employee Participation in Ownership and Management, 1987; Publication (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - "Litigation in 2050: A Backward-Forward, Topsy-Turvy Look at Dispute Resolutions"., Publication (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: Litigation in 2050: A Backward-Forward, Topsy-Turvy Look at Dispute Resolutions, Essay, 1991; Publication (Box 9, Folder 22)
      Author: Lawrence J. Fox
  - Top Executive Compensation in US-Based Multinationals: The 1986 Edition., Publication (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: Top Executive Compensation in U.S.-Based Multinationals, 1986 Edition, Publication (Box 9, Folder 23)
      Author: Harland Fox and Charles A. Peck
  - "Update on Skill-Based Pay"., 1989; Publication (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: Update on Skill-Based Pay, 1989; Publication (Box 9, Folder 24)
      Author: Fred Luthans and Marilyn L. Fox
  - Collective Bargaining Films: A Critical Survey., 1990; Publication (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Item 1: Is Pattern Bargaining Dead? A Discussion, 1990; Publication (Box 9, Folder 25)
      Notes: response to Kathryn J. Ready's article
  - "Employee Committees: What Effect are They Having?", 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: Employee Committees: What Effect Are They Having?, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 26)
      Author: Dennis J. Franecki, Ralph F. Catalanello, and Curtiss K. Behrens
  - "Productivity Initiatives at USDA"., 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: Productivity Initiatives at USDA, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 27)
      Author: J.J. Franke
  - Employee Participation in Decision Making in the Metal and Engineering Industry., 1986; Publication (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: Employee participation in decision making in the metal and engineering industry, 1986; Publication (Box 9, Folder 28)
      Author: Stephen J. Frenkel
  - "Underload and Overload in Working Life: Outlines of a Multidisciplinary Approach"., 1976; Publication (Box 9, Folder 29)
    September 1976
    - Item 1: Underload and Overload in Working Life: Outline of a Multidisciplinary Approach, 1976; Publication (Box 9, Folder 29)
      Author: Marianne Frankenhaeuser and Bertil Gardell
  - "New Diversity in the American Workplace: A Challenge to Arbitration"., 1992; Publication (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Item 1: New Diversity in the American Workplace: A Challenge to Arbitration, 1992; Publication (Box 9, Folder 30)
      Author: Bruce Fraser
  - "My Years on the Chrysler Board"., 1986; Publication (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Item 1: My years on the Chrysler Board, 1986; Publication (Box 9, Folder 31)
      Author: Douglas A. Fraser
  - "A Fundamental Change in Wage Bargaining"., 1982; Publication (Box 9, Folder 32)
    July - August 1982
    - Item 1: A Fundamental Change in Wage Bargaining, 1982; Publication (Box 9, Folder 32)
      Author: Audrey Freedman
  - A Roundtable on Industrial Policy., 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Item 1: A Roundtable on Industrial Policy: Discussions of an American Productivity Center Computer Network, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - "Executive Summary of Employment Security vs. Labor Market Flexibility"., 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 34)
    April 5 1984
    - Item 1: Executive Summary of Employment Security vs. Labor Market Flexibility, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - "How the 1980s Have Changed Industrial Relations"., 1988; Publication (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Item 1: How the 1980's have changed industrial relations, 1988; Publication (Box 9, Folder 35)
      Notes: also published in Monthly Labor Review, 2 copies in folder
  - Human Resources Outlook 1988., 1987; Publication (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Item 1: Human Resources Outlook 1988, 1987; Publication (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Perspectives on Employment., 1986; Publication (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Item 1: Perspectives on Employment, 1986; Publication (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - "Plant Closed -- No Jobs"., 1980; Publication (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Item 1: Plant Closed--No Jobs: An examinations of the effects of legislation proposed to 'soften the blow' of plant closing, 1980; Publication (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - The New Look in Wage Policy and Employee Relations., 1985; Publication (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Item 1: The New Look in Wage Policy and Employee Relations, 1985; Publication (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - "The Compensation Program: Balancing Organizational and Employee Needs"., 1982; Publication (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: The Compensation Program: Balancing Organizational and Employee Needs, 1982; Publication (Box 9, Folder 40)
      Author: Sara M. Freedman, Robert T. Keller and John R. Montanari
  - Crumbling Pillar? Declining Union density in Japan., 1989; Publication (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Item 1: Crumbling Pillar? Declining Union Density in Japan, 1989; Publication (Box 9, Folder 41)
      Author: Richard B. Freeman and Marcus E. Rebick
  - "What Does the Future Hold for US Unionism?"., 1988; Publication (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Item 1: What Does the Future Hold for U.S. Unionism?, 1988; Publication (Box 9, Folder 42)
      Author: Richard B. Freeman
  - "Flexible Automation: Implications for Work and the Economy"., 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 43)
    December 13 - 14 1983
    - Item 1: Flexible Automation: Implications for Work and the Economy, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 43)
      Author: Peter Unterweger
  - "Industrial Relations and Technology: The French Case"., 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Item 1: Industrial Relations and Technology: The French Case, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 44)
      Author: Guy Groux
  - "Position Paper of the General Confederation of Labor on the Introduction of New Technologies and the Role of Working Class Unions"., 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Item 1: Position Paper of the General Confederation of Labor, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 45)
      Author: Ernest Deis
  - "Reactic and Quality Circles"., 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 46)
    December 13 - 14 1983.
    - Item 1: Reactic and Quality Circles, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 46)
      Author: Herve Serieyx
  - "Robotics and Micro-Electronics on the Shop Floor: New Challenges for the Workers' Movement"., 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Item 1: Robotics and Micro-Electronics on the Shop Floor: New Challenges for the Workers Movement, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 47)
      Author: Benjamin Coriat
  - "The CFDT and Technological Change"., 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Item 1: The Confederated Union of Engineers and Managers and Technological Change, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 48)
      Author: Yves Lasfargues
  - "Reflections on Business and Technology"., 1988; Publication (Box 9, Folder 49)
    October 1988
    - Item 1: Reflections on Business and Technology, 1988; Publication (Box 9, Folder 49)
      Author: Donald N. Frey
  - "The Current State of the Israeli Labor Movement -- Time for Reform"., Publication (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Item 1: The Current State of the Israeli Labor Movement - Time for Reform, Publication (Box 9, Folder 50)
      Author: Abraham Friedman
  - "Child Care for Employees' Kids"., 1986; Publication (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Item 1: Child care for employees' kids, 1986; Publication (Box 9, Folder 51)
      Author: Dana E. Friedman
  - "Eldercare: The Employee Benefit of the 1990s?"., 1986; Publication (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Item 1: Eldercare: The Employee Benefit of the 1990s?, 1986; Publication (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - "Work vs. Family: War of the Worlds"., 1987; Publication (Box 9, Folder 53)
    August 1987
    - Item 1: Work vs. Family: War of the Worlds, 1987; Publication (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - "Joint Training in Negotiations As A Strategy for Encouraging More Cooperative Approaches to Collective Bargaining"., 1990; Publication (Box 9, Folder 54)
    August 1990
    - Item 1: Joint Training in Negotiation as A Strategy for Encouraging More Cooperative Approaches to Collective Bargaining, 1990; Publication (Box 9, Folder 54)
      Author: Raymond Friedman, Charles Heckscher, Chip Hunter, Robert McKersie, Elaine Landry, Lawrence Susskind
  - "Trust, Understanding and Control: Factors Affecting Support for Mutual Gains Bargaining in Labor Negotiations"., 1992; Publication (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Item 1: Trust, Understanding, and Control: Factors Affecting Support for Mutual Gains Bargaining in Labor Negotiations, 1992; Publication (Box 9, Folder 55)
      Author: Raymond A. Friedman
  - "Unionized Employment Relationships: A New Approach. B. Mutual Gains Bargaining for Higher Education"., 1990; Publication (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Item 1: Collective Bargaining in Higher Education: The 1990s, Publication (Box 9, Folder 56)
      Notes: in Collective Bargaining in Higher Education: The 1990s, Proceedings of 18th annual conference edited by Joel M. Douglas
  - "Productivity and Quality -- Unlocking America's Strengths: Participative Ownership: A Competitive Necessity"., 1985; Publication (Box 9, Folder 57)
    April 30 1985
    - Item 1: Productivity and Quality--Unlocking America's Strengths: Participative Ownership, A Competitive Necessity, 1985; Publication (Box 9, Folder 57)
      Author: Carl F. Frost
  - "The Scanlon Plan: Anyone for Free Enterprise?"., 1978; Publication (Box 9, Folder 58)
    Winter 1978
    - Item 1: The Scanlon Plan: Anyone for Free Enterprise?, 1978; Publication (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - "Relating to Robots"., 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Item 1: Relating to Robots, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 59)
      Author: Neil Frude
  - "Collective Bargaining in Japan: Recent Trends and Problems"., 1987; Publication (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Item 1: Collective bargaining in Japan: Recent trends and Problems, 1987; Publication (Box 9, Folder 60)
      Author: Iwao Fujiwara
  - "Becoming the Organization of the Future"., 1981; Publication (Box 9, Folder 61)
    Summer 1981
    - Item 1: Becoming the Organization of the Future, 1981; Publication (Box 9, Folder 61)
      Author: Stephen H. Fuller
  - "How Quality-of-Worklife Projects Work for General Motors"., 1980; Publication (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Item 1: How quality-of-worklife projects work for General Motors, 1980; Publication (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - "How to Become the Organization of the Future"., 1980; Publication (Box 9, Folder 63)
    February 1980
    - Item 1: How to become the organization of the future, 1980; Publication (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - "How to Construct and Use a Productivity Index"., 1988; Publication (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Item 1: How to Construct and Use a Productivity Loss Index, 1988; Publication (Box 9, Folder 64)
      Author: F. Timothy Fuller
  - "A Resurrection Plan for Dying Factories"., 1985; Publication (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Item 1: A Resurrection Plan for Dying Factories, 1985; Publication (Box 9, Folder 65)
      Author: William E. Fulmer
  - "Industrial Democracy in Other Countries"., 1977; Publication (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Item 1: Industrial Democracy in Other Countries, 1977; Publication (Box 9, Folder 66)
      Author: James C. Furlong
      Notes: in Labor in the Boardroom
  - "Mitbestimmung and the US"., 1977; Publication (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Item 1: Mitbestimmung and the U.S., 1977; Publication (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - "Co-Determination and Its Contribution to Industrial Democracy: A Critical Evaluation"., 1980; Publication (Box 9, Folder 68)
    September 5 - 7 1980
    - Item 1: Codetermination and Its Contribution to Industrial Democracy: A Critical Evaluation, 1980; Publication (Box 9, Folder 68)
      Author: Friedrich Furstenberg
  - "Firm Awaits 'Magic' of Japanese"., 1987; Publication (Box 9, Folder 69)
    May 24 1987
    - Item 1: Firm Awaits 'Magic' of Japanese: Kentucky Manufacturer Still Losing Money After Takeover Six Years Ago, 1987; Publication (Box 9, Folder 69)
      Author: Mark H. Furstenberg
  - "Getting the Most from Teamwork"., 1991; Publication (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Item 1: Getting the Most from Teamwork, 1991; Publication (Box 9, Folder 70)
      Author: Mary Ann Castronovo Fusco
  - "Labor-Managed and Participatory Firms: A Review Article"., 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 71)
    September 1983
    - Item 1: Labor-Managed and Participatory Firms: A Review Article, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 71)
      Author: Daniel R. Fusfeld
  - "GM's Work Life EffortsAn Interview with Howard C. Carlson"., 1978; Publication (Box 9, Folder 72)
    July - August 1978
    - Item 1: GM's Quality of Work Life Efforts An Interview with Howard C. Carlson, 1978; Publication (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - "Rewarding Individual and Team Productivity: The Biloxi Merit Bonus Plan"., 1985; Publication (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Item 1: Rewarding Individual and Team Productivity: The Biloxi Merit Bonus Plan, 1985; Publication (Box 9, Folder 73)
      Author: Gerald T. Gabris, Kenneth Mitchell and Ronald McLemore
  - "Women and the United Auto Workers in the 1940's and 1950's: Reconstructing Their Story"., 1989; Publication (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Item 1: Sources for Studying Labor at the Western Historical Collections of the University of Colorado, Boulder, 1989; Publication (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - "The Employer's Duty to Bargain on Termination of Unit Work -- Part I"., 1981; Publication (Box 9, Folder 75)
    October 1981
    - Item 1: The Employer's Duty to Bargain On Termination of Unit Work, 1981; Publication (Box 9, Folder 75)
      Author: Stanley A. Gacek
  - "The Employer's Duty to Bargain on Termination of Work -- Part II"., 1981; Publication (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Item 1: The Employer's Duty to Bargain on Termination of Unit Work, 1981; Publication (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - "Worker Participation and Organizational Change in Shipbuilding: A International Review"., 1982; Publication (Box 9, Folder 77)
    September 14 - 16 1982
    - Item 1: Worker Participation and Organizational Change in Shipbuilding: An International Review, 1982; Publication (Box 9, Folder 77)
      Author: Michael E. Gaffney
  - Making the Competitive Connection: Strategic Management and Training., 1989; Publication (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Item 1: Making the Competitive Connection: Strategic Management in Training, 1989; Publication (Box 9, Folder 78)
      Author: Leila J. Gainer
  - "Staying Alive: Jack Grayson on the American Productivity Crisis"., 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 79)
    January 1984
    - Item 1: Staying Alive: Jack Grayson on the American Productivity Crisis, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 79)
      Author: Patricia Galagan
  - "Work Teams that Work"., 1986; Publication (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - Item 1: Work Teams that Work, 1986; Publication (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - "Can More Capital Buy Higher Productivity?"., 1980; Publication (Box 9, Folder 81)